A tornado flew around the court before he played
Excuse the mess it made, the crowd got swept away
Rings I see him shine, they hang up in the sky
Still here still grinding, things are slowing down
I've been thinking about you, you now now now
I've been thinking about you, LeBro Bro Bro
I've been thinking about you, do you hear the slander still?
Do ya, do ya?
Do you not think they know the truth?
'Cause I've been thinking about LeBron Bron, how about you?
'Cause I've been thinking about LeBron (ooh)
No I don't hate 'em, I just thought they lost their damn perception
Got a stat line no one touching, check numbers twice
Just they call and whine, start just laughing
Now watching dropping thirty
These kids and all they don't know he's done it all before
I've been thinking about you, you now now now
I've been thinking about you, LeBro Bro Bro
I've been thinking about you, do you hear the slander still?
Do ya, do ya?
Do you not think they know the truth?
'Cause I've been thinking about LeBron Bron (ooh)
'Cause I've been thinking about LeBron, how about you?
How about you, yes of course
I remember, how could I forget about LaBla
You know, you took that soap back, a game savant
It will never get old, not if you're so nutty
The spirit of the game is yours
We will look down this road until they finally stop pretending you ain't the GOAT
Do you not think they know the truth?
'Cause I've been thinking about LeBron Bron
'Cause I've been thinking about LeBron